Guide to the Seymour Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Seymour Family: General, (1746-1851)-1942; Series I; 5" (1 box)
  - Early Papers
    - Seymour, Charles (1777-1852): correspondence from Nathan Perkins Seymour, 1841-1851 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
      See also: box 104, folders 1-2
    - Seymour, Charles (1777-1852): account book, 1817-[1823?] (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Seymour, Charles (1777-1852): memorabilia, 1850 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Seymour, Charles (1807-1886): correspondence from Charles Seymour (1777-1852), 1847 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Seymour, Charles (1807-1886): correspondence from Nathan Perkins Seymour, 1843, 1851 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Seymour, Charles (1807-1886): printed material, 1813 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Seymour, Emily: correspondence from Mary Parker, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Seymour, Isaac (1723-1755): miscellaneous papers, 1752-1755 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - [Seymour, Jacob?]: receipt, 1746 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Seymour, Julia: correspondence from Elizabeth (Day) Seymour, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Seymour, Julia: pamphlet by Joseph Emerson, The Evangelical Primer, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Seymour, Moses (1710/11-1795): receipts, 1779, 1780 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Seymour, Thomas (1735-1829): miscellaneous papers, 1750-1784, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
      See also: box 104, folder 4
  - Genealogical Material
    - [Day Family branch?], 1841-1846 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Leggett Family, 1872, 1931, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Seymour Family, pre1800-1942 (Box 1, Folder 18-24)
      General
      See also: box 114, folder 1-2
      See also: box 104, folder 5
    - "The Royal Arms and Noble Ancestry of the American Seymours," The Journal of American History, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Nathan Perkins Seymour, 1801-1891; Series II; 1'3" (3 boxes)
  Nathan Perkins Seymour was born December 24, 1813, at Hartford, Connecticut. His parents were Charles Seymour, a prominent Hartford merchant, and his wife Catharine Perkins Seymour. Nathan Perkins Seymour attended the Hopkins Grammar School of Hartford and graduated from Yale University in the class of 1834. For two years he served as rector of the Hopkins Grammar School and then returned to Yale as a tutor. In 1840 he became chairman of the classics department at Western Reserve College in Hudson, Ohio, a post which he was to hold until 1870. On September 7, 1841, he married Elizabeth Day of Hartford.
  As a professor emeritus Seymour continued an active intellectual life. From 1870 until 1891 he delivered regular lectures at Western Reserve College, Lake Erie Seminary at Painesville, and at other schools in Ohio. Each spring from 1879 until 1891 he taught at Miss Porter's School in Farmington, Connecticut, and in January and February, 1885, he was a guest lecturer on English literature at Yale.
  In 1890 Seymour accepted the offer of his younger son, Thomas Day Seymour, to move to New Haven and live with Thomas' family. However, Seymour's sojourn in New Haven was short. Just before Thanksgiving, 1891, he contracted influenza, suffered complications because of a fall on Christmas Eve, and died on December 28, 1891.
  Nathan Perkins Seymour's life revolved around his academic career and his family. Correspondence with family members includes discussions of his research and issues confronting the schools at which he taught, such as coeducation at Western Reserve College. One will also find material on the social life of Hartford and of Ohio, theories of child rearing, and descriptions of travel in the U.S., as well as general family matters. Letters to Thomas Day Seymour (in Series VII) are particularly numerous.
  This series is divided into four sections.
  Correspondence contains letters addressed to Nathan Perkins Seymour, letters from Seymour to non-family members, and some correspondence between non-family members which came into Seymour's possession. In each of these sub-sections, the correspondence is arranged alphabetically by sender. Within each folder the letters are arranged chronologically. Of particular interest are Thomas Day Seymour's letters to his father wherein he discusses his scholarly work and travels as well as family life.
  Writings consists of miscellaneous original writings and translations by Seymour.
  Printed Material is made up of several small books and pamphlets owned by Seymour and copies of an obituary notice and memorial pamphlets which appeared shortly after his death.
  Personal and Memorabilia consists of one folder containing account books, receipts, and bookplates.
  - Correspondence
    - Nathan Perkins Seymour from
      - Allen, Frederic D., 1880 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1887 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Dean, Katharine Seymour (Parsons), 1885, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Parsons, Sarah Day (Seymour), 1865, 1866 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Parsons, William Cheney, 1871 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Seymour, Charles (1843-1913), 1862-1885, undated (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
        See also: box 104, folder 6
      - Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1865-1888, undated (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
      - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), 1881 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1865-1882 (Box 2, Folder 11-22)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1883-1889 (Box 3, Folder 23-35)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1890-1891 (Box 4, Folder 36-39)
      - Sill, Edward R., 1870-1885 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Nathan Perkins Seymour to
      - "Catherine", undated (Box 4, Folder 40a)
      - "My Dear Niece", undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - "Sister", 1888 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - To Others from Others:
      - To "Mother of Mrs. Green" from Michelet, Jules, 1865 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - To Harris, from unidentified, 1862 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - To faculty of Western Reserve College from Long, C., 1851 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Writings
    - Autobiographical chronology, 1850-1887 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Sermon, church resolution, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Translations, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - The Mint [edited by Nathan Perkins Seymour?], 1834 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Printed Material
    - Small books and pamphlets, 1819-1857, undated (Box 4, Folder 50-51)
    - American Railway Guides for the U.S., 1851-1853, 1855-1856 (Box 4, Folder 51a)
    - Webster, Daniel, Funeral Oration, 1801 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Articles re: Nathan Perkins Seymour's house in Hudson, Ohio
      See: box 107, folder 68
    - Memorials, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Obituaries, 1891 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Personal and Memorabilia
    - Account books, book plates, 1829, 1837-1850, undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Elizabeth (Day) Seymour, 1845-1900; Series III; 5" (1 box)
  Elizabeth (Day) Seymour was born February 16, 1816, the second of the eight children of Thomas and Sarah Coit Day of Hartford, Connecticut. She attended a series of private schools, including Catherine Beecher's Female Seminary. On September 7, 1841, she married Nathan Perkins Seymour, and in the years that followed they had four children: Charles (1843), Sarah Day (1845), Thomas Day (1848), and Harriet, who was born March 27, 1856, and lived for only two days.
  For fifty years Elizabeth made her home in Hudson, Ohio, though each year she made an extended trip to Hartford. When Western Reserve College moved to Cleveland (1881), Nathan was often away for days and weeks at a time, and Elizabeth, who found herself in a large empty house, became increasingly lonely and ill.
  In 1891 she and Nathan moved to join son Thomas in New Haven, but Nathan died within a few months. In the years following his death Elizabeth was often bedridden. She died September 7, 1900.
  This series is divided into the following sections.
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by sender, and chronologically within each folder.
  Writings consists of one folder containing an incomplete, undated memoir by Elizabeth (Day) Seymour.
  Personal and Memorabilia consists of one folder containing handwritten copies of hymns and poems, religions tracts, an invitation, and a calling card.
  - Correspondence
    - Elizabeth (Day) Seymour from
      - A-Z (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Andrews, Catharine Augusta (Day), 1850, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Andrews, Laura Day, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1890 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Cutler, Francis E., 1887, 1891-1892 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Day, Edward L., [1892] (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Day, Harriet, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Day, Sarah (Coit), 1861-1862 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Day, Thomas M., 1891 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Dean, Katharine (Parsons), 1885-1900 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - [Ely, Mary F. (Day)?], 1845-1849, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Holley, Sarah Coit (Day), 1892 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Jackson, Katherine D., undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Long, R.E., 1893, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Parsons, Harriet, [1892] (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Parsons, Sarah (Seymour), 1871-1892, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Putnam, Harriette (Day), undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Rudd, Maria C. Holley, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - St. John, Clara (Seymour), 1887-1891 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Seymour, Charles (1843-1913), 1863-1893, undated (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
        See also: box 104, folder 7-8
      - Seymour, Nathan Perkins, 1883-1891, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1856-1893, undated (Box 5, Folder 23-24)
      - Williamson, Edith Ely, 1892-1895 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Writings
    - Memoir, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Personal and Memorabilia
    - Certificates
      See: box 114, folder 1
    - Miscellaneous, 1891, 1893, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Day Family, 1711-1897; Series IV; 5" (1 box)
  DAY FAMILY contains the papers of Elizabeth (Day) Seymour's parents, siblings, and of the siblings' children. (Other papers of the Day Family will be found in the Day Family Papers, MSS Group Number 175.) The parents, Thomas Day (1777-1855) and Sarah (Coit) Day (1786-1865), were married on March 18, 1813, and made Hartford, Connecticut, their permanent home. They had eight children. Thomas served from 1810-1835 as secretary of the state of Connecticut and from 1825-1833 as chief judge of the Hartford County Court.
  Two of the eight children achieved prominence in Hartford civic life. Sarah Coit (Day) Holley (1814-1899) married Connecticut's lieutenant governor, and soon to be governor, Alexander Hamilton Holley. Son Thomas Mills Day graduated from Yale College, studied law with his father, and published a digest of Connecticut law reports in 1840. From 1855-1865 he served as editor of the Hartford Courant.
  The series is divided into the following sections.
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by recipient. For each recipient, the senders are in separate, alphabetically-arranged folders. Within each folder the material is in chronological order.
  Writings consists of the memoirs of several members of the family, arranged alphabetically by author. Of particular interest is the memoir by Sarah (Day) Holley. In it she mentions her friendship with the Beecher family, the religious revival in Hartford in 1821, her introduction to Martin Van Buren, and the hard times of the economic slump in 1839. Catharine (Day) Andrews' memoir is especially rich for its views of nineteenth century Hartford.
  Legal Records consists of a pair of legal documents of Jeremiah Day.
  Printed Material. consists of two publications and an obituary.
  - Correspondence
    - Andrews, Catharine (Day): from Holley, Sarah (Day), 1885, 1891-1894 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Andrews, Catharine (Day): from Putnam, Harriet (Day), undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Andrews, Catharine (Day): from Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1844-1847 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Day, Sarah (Coit): from Cott, Hannah (Abel), 1829 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Day, Sarah (Coit): from Ely, Mary Frances (Day), 1846 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Day, Sarah (Coit): from Haven, H.L., undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Day, Sarah (Coit): from Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1837-1865, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Day, Sarah (Coit): from Williams, Rebecca, 1864 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Day, Thomas: from Andrews, Catharine (Day); Day, Sarah (Coit); Holley, Sarah (Day); Putnam, Harriette (Day); Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1839 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Day, Thomas: from Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1828, [1855?] (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Day, Thomas: from Willard, Emma, 1842 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - [Day, Thomas Mills?]: from [Ely, Mary (Day)?], [1849?] (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Day, Thomas Mills: from Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Day, Thomas Mills: from Seymour, Thomas Day, 1865-1897, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Ely, Mary (Day): from Seymour, Thomas Day, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Holley, Sarah (Day): from Andrews, Catharine (Day), undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Holley, Sarah (Day): from Ely, Mary (Day), 1842-1891 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Holley, Sarah (Day): from Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1829-1865, undated (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
    - Putnam, Harriette (Day): from Andrews, Catharine (Day), undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Putnam, Harriette (Day): from Ely, Mary (Day), undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Putnam, Harriette (Day): from Hickok, L.P., 1853 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Putnam, Harriette (Day): from Metcalf, Julia, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Putnam, Harriette (Day): from Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1841, 1856, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Putnam, Harriette (Day): from Seymour, Thomas Day, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Day, Henry Noble: to Oviatt, Heman, 1853 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Holley, Sarah (Day): to "Sisters", undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Seymour, Elizabeth (Day): to "Sisters", 1853 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Unidentified, 1841, 1845, 1892, 1924, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Writings
    - Andrews, Catharine (Day): memoir, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Day, Thomas (1777-1855): diary of studies, 1792-1794 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Ely, Mary (Day): memoir, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Holley, Sarah (Day): memoir (addendum by Thomas M. Day), 1893 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      See also: box 104, folder 9
  - Legal Records
    - Day, Jeremiah: marriage certificate, 1773 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Day, Jeremiah: miscellaneous, 1711-1769 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      See also: box 104, folder 10
  - Printed Material
    - J. Bunyan, Heart's Ease in Heart-Trouble, 1762 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Lowell Mason & G.J. Webb, The Juvenile Singing School, 1838 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Obituary: Harriet Day Andrews, [1891?] (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Charles Seymour (1843-1913), 1869-1907; Series V; 0.25; (1 box)
  Charles Seymour (1843-1913) was the eldest child of Nathan Perkins and Elizabeth Day Seymour. He was born on December 20, 1843, in Hudson, Ohio, and lived there until his graduation from Western Reserve College in 1864. He then moved to Knoxville, Tennessee, and established a law practice. He specialized in real estate developments and represented large interests (often from other states and countries) who sought to develop the undeveloped frontier land of Tennessee.
  Like so many others in his family, Charles loved to travel. He visited most of the United States and was delighted that his business brought him to England twice each year. He greatly enjoyed taking his nieces and nephews with him on his trips abroad. It was he who arranged for the superb foreign education of his nephew and namesake, the future president of Yale University, Charles Seymour (1885-1963).
  In 1889 he was injured in a train wreck which left him lame. In time he returned to the round of business and travel. He suffered several heart attacks in the last years of his life and died April 12, 1913.
  This series is divided into two sections.
  Correspondence contains all the letters addressed to Charles Seymour, arranged alphabetically by sender and chronologically within each folder. At the end of this section there is one letter from Charles Seymour to a cousin and a copy of a letter from a Mr. Mead to a Mr. McGuffey in which the former discussed the injuries sustained by Charles Seymour in a train wreck in Tennessee in 1889.
  Printed Material consists of an advertisement and a document on farm leases.
  - Correspondence
    - Charles Seymour (1843-1913)
      - from Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - from Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1907 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - from Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1877, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - from Seymour, Nathan Perkins, 1880 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - from Seymour, Thomas Day, 1869-1907, undated (Box 7, Folder 5-8)
      - to Putnam, Katharine Day, 1848 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - To Mead, Mr. [underline] from McGuffey, Mr. [underline], 1889 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Printed Material
    - Advertisement for Cockrill & Seymour, Real Estate Brokers in East Tennessee, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Report for East Tennessee by the International Land and Labour Agency, Birmingham, for the sale and lease of farms in the United States, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Report on the Group Plan of Public Building of the City of Cleveland Ohio (Folder 115)
- Parson - Dean Families, 1863-1949; Series VI; 3'9" (9 boxes)
  This series contains the papers of Sarah Day (Seymour) Parsons, her husband and children. The papers are divided into the following sections.
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by family member. Within each folder the material is arranged chronologically.
  Writings contains a variety of journals and notebooks on such topics as music, religion, and travel, arranged alphabetically by author.
  Printed Material is arranged by category of material.
  Personal and Memorabilia is arranged in roughly chronological order.
  - Correspondence
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from A-R, 1892-1942, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from S-Z, unidentified, 1898-1942, n.d (Box 8, Folder 1a)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Andrews, Julia, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1915, 1930-1941 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Angel, Henry Seymour, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Angel, John, 1924-1944 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from [Blauvert, Mary?], 1916-1945, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Day, Arthur, 1912, 1930-1934 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Day, Sarah (Coit), 1908-1939 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Dean, Lee Maltbie, 1927-1933, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Ellinte, Janet J., undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Fromkes, Eva and Maurice, 1920, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Garmany, Carrie, 1912-1943, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Holden, Margaretta, 1909-1930 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Holley, Sarah Coit (Day), 1891 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Jackson, Rose, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Keep, Elizabeth, 1907, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from McClure, Helen, 1925-1930, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Katharine (parsons) Dean: from Mason, Mary, 1901-1946, undated (Box 8a, Folder 18)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Monier, Helen Warren (Hall), 1925, 1927 (Box 8a, Folder 19)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parker, Horatio, 1900-1915, undated (Box 8a, Folder 20)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parlow, Minnie, 1929, undated (Box 8a, Folder 21)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, Barrie (O'Neill), 1943-1946 (Box 8a, Folder 22)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, Charles Seymour, 1882-1904 (Box 8a, Folder 23)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, Christina, undated (Box 8a, Folder 24)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, Dorothy, 1927-1944 (Box 8a, Folder 25)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, Harriet Day, 1900-1949, undated (Box 8a, Folder 26-30)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, Hugh Galt, 1934-1945 (Box 8a, Folder 31)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, Mary (Blackman), 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, Myra, 1911-1946 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, Robert, 1906-1917, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, Robert, Jr., [1927?]-1946 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean; from Parsons, Sarah Day (Seymour), 1901-1934, undated (Box 9, Folder 36-36c)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, Seymour, 1928-1946 (Box 9a, Folder 37)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, William C., 1900-1917, undated (Box 9a, Folder 38)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Parsons, William E., 1884-1939, undated (Box 9a, Folder 39)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Reynolds, Alice E., 1934-1939 (Box 9a, Folder 40)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Rogers, Edward Pendleton, 1919 (Box 9a, Folder 41)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from St. John, Clara (Seymour), 1905-1946, undated (Box 9a, Folder 42)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Seymour, Charles (1843-1913), 1889-1917, undated (Box 9a, Folder 43-43a)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1901-1937 (Box 9a, Folder 44)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Seymour, Charles, Jr., 1938 (Box 9a, Folder 45)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Stanton, Louise (Parsons), 1921-1946, undated (Box 9a, Folder 46)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from [Wilkinson, Harriet?], 1930 (Box 9a, Folder 47)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from "Betty", 1936-1937, undated (Box 9a, Folder 48)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from "Aunt Nellie", [1920?] (Box 9a, Folder 49)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from "Katharine", 1910 (Box 9a, Folder 50)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: from Unidentified, 1914-1919 (Box 9a, Folder 51)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: to Frank, [underline], 1950 (Box 9a, Folder 52)
    - Katharine (Parsons) Dean: to Garmany, Carrie, 1931 (Box 9a, Folder 53)
    - Lee Maltbie Dean: from A-Z, unidentified, undated (Box 9a, Folder 54)
    - Lee Maltbie Dean: from Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1930 (Box 9a, Folder 55)
    - Lee Maltbie Dean: from Boyd, Morrison C., 1949 (Box 9a, Folder 56)
    - Lee Maltbie Dean: from Carlsen, Dines, 1946 (Box 9a, Folder 57)
    - Lee Maltbie Dean: from Dean, Katharine (Parsons), 1927-1930, undated (Box 9a, Folder 58-60)
    - Lee Maltbie Dean: from Parsons, Robert, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Lee Maltbie Dean: from [Stanton?], Louise, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Lee Maltbie Dean: from Stokowski, Leopold, undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Lee Maltbie Dean: to "Aunt Mary," "Aunt Frances", 1936 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Mrs. Lee P. Dean: from Parsons, Elizabeth, 1890 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Charles Seymour Parsons: from Dean, Katharine (Parsons), unidentified, 1894, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Harriet Day Parsons: from A-Z unidentified, 1899-1945, undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Harriet Day-Parsons: from Dean, Katharine (Parsons), 1899-1915, undated (Box 10, Folder 68-69)
    - Myra Parsons: from A-Z, 1919-1920 (Box 10, Folder 69a)
    - Myra Parsons: from Parsons, Robert Day, 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Myra Parsons: from Parsons, Sarah (Seymour), [1914?] (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Myra Parsons: from Parsons, Seymour, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Sarah (Seymour) Parsons: from A-Z, unidentified, 1890-1932, undated (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Sarah (Seymour) Parsons: from Parsons, Harriet Day, 1906-1918, undated (Box 10, Folder 73a)